One summer afternoon in 2013,
بعد ظهر أحد الأيام الصيفيّة في عام 2013،
DC police detained, questioned and searched a man
اعتقَلَت واستجوبَت وفتشَت شرطة واشنطن رجلاً
who appeared suspicious and potentially dangerous.
والذي بدا مشبوهًا ويحتمل أن يكون خطرًا.
This wasn't what I was wearing the day of the detention, to be fair,
ليس هذا هو ما كنت أرتديه يوم اعتقالي، حتى أكون منصفًا،
but I have a picture of that as well.
ولكن لدي صورةٌ لذلك أيضًا.
I know it's very frightening -- try to remain calm.
أنا أعلم أنه مخيفٌ جدًّا -- حاولوا التزام الهدوء.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
At this time, I was interning
في ذلك الوقت، كنت أجري تدريبًا
at the Public Defender Service in Washington DC,
في المديرية العامة للدفاع في واشنطن العاصمة،
and I was visiting a police station for work.
وكنت في زيارة لأحد مراكز الشرطة من أجل عمل.
I was on my way out,
كنت في طريقي للخروج،
and before I could make it to my car,
وقبل الوصول إلى سيارتي،
two police cars pulled up to block my exit,
توقفت سيارتين تابعتين للشرطة لمنعي من الخروج.
and an officer approached me from behind.
و اقترب مني ضابط من الخلف.
He told me to stop, take my backpack off
طلب مني التّوقف ونَزْعَ حقيبتي
and put my hands on the police car parked next to us.
وأن أضع يَدَيّ على غطاء محرك السيارة المركونة بجانبنا.
About a dozen officers then gathered near us.
تجمّع حوالي عشرة ضباط بالقرب منّا.
All of them had handguns,
كانوا جميعًا يحملون مسدسات،
some had assault rifles.
وبعضهم كان يحمل بنادق هجومية.
They rifled through my backpack.
فتَّشوا حقيبتي.
They patted me down.
ثم قاموا بتفتيشي.
They took pictures of me spread on the police car,
أخذوا صورًا لي ممدود الذراعين فوق سيارة الشرطة،
and they laughed.
وضحكوا.
And as all this was happening --
وأثناء حدوث كل هذا --
as I was on the police car trying to ignore the shaking in my legs,
حينما كنت في سيارة الشرطة أحاول تجاهل ارتجاف ساقيّ،
trying to think clearly about what I should do --
والتفكير بوضوح حول ما يجب عليّ فعله --
something stuck out to me as odd.
بدا لي شيء ما غريبًا.
When I look at myself in this photo,
حينما أنظر إلى نفسي في هذه الصورة،
if I were to describe myself,
إذا كان عليّ وصف نفسي،
I think I'd say something like,
أنا أعتقد أنني سأقول شيئًا مثل،
"19-year-old Indian male, bright T-shirt, wearing glasses."
"ذكر هندي يبلغ من العمر 19 عامًا، تي شيرت ملوَّن، يرتدي نظارات."
But they weren't including any of these details.
ولكنّهم لم يذكروا أيًّا من هذه التفاصيل.
Into their police radios as they described me,
في الإذاعة الخاصة بالشرطة أثناء وصفهم لي،
they kept saying, "Middle Eastern male with a backpack.
استمروا بالقول: "ذكرٌ شرق أوسطي يحمل حقيبة ظهر.
Middle Eastern male with a backpack."
ذكرٌ شرق أوسطي يحمل حقيبة ظهر."
And this description carried on into their police reports.
واستمرّ تداول هذا الوصف في التقارير الشرطيّة الخاصة بهم.
I never expected to be described by my own government in these terms:
لم أكن أتوقع أبدًا أن تصفني حكومة بلدي بهذه الأوصاف:
"lurking,"
"متربّص"،
"nefarious,"
"شنيع"،
"terrorist."
"إرهابيّ".
And the detention dragged on like this.
واستمر احتجازي على نفس الوتيرة.
They sent dogs trained to smell explosives to sweep the area I'd been in.
أرسلوا كلابًا مدربة على شم رائحة المتفجرات لمسح المنطقة التي كنت أتواجد بها.
They called the federal government to see if I was on any watch lists.
اتصلوا بالحكومة الاتحادية لمعرفة ما إذا كنت على أي لوائح مراقبة.
They sent a couple of detectives to cross-examine me on why,
أرسلوا اثنين من رجال المباحث لاستجوابي حول لماذا،
if I claimed I had nothing to hide,
إذا ادعيت أنني لم يكن لدي ما أخفيه،
I wouldn't consent to a search of my car.
ما كنت لأوافق على تفتيش سيارتي.
And I could see they weren't happy with me,
وكنت أستطيع رؤية أنهم لم يكونوا راضين عني،
but I felt I had no way of knowing what they'd want to do next.
ولكنني شعرت أنه لم تكن لدي أية وسيلة لمعرفة ما كانوا يريدون فعله بعد ذلك.
At one point, the officer who patted me down
في لحظة ما، تفحّص الضابط الذي قام بتفتيشي
scanned the side of the police station to see where the security camera was
جهة مركز الشرطة ليحدد مكان تواجد الكاميرا الأمنية
to see how much of this was being recorded.
لمعرفة مقدار ما تمّ تسجيله.
And when he did that,
وعندما فعل ذلك،
it really sank in how completely I was at their mercy.
استوعبت فعليًّا أنني كنت تمامًا تحت رحمتهم.
I think we're all normalized from a young age
أعتقد أننا جميعًا تعوَّدنا منذ سن مبكرة
to the idea of police officers and arrests and handcuffs,
على فكرة وجود ضباط الشرطة والاعتقالات والقيود،
so it's easy to forget how demeaning and coercive a thing it is
لذلك فمن السهل نسيان كم هو مهينٌ وقسريّ
to seize control over another person's body.
أن تُسيطر على شخص آخر.
I know it sounds like the point of my story
أنا أعلم أنه يبدو وكأن محور قصتي
is how badly treated I was because of my race --
هو مدى سوء المعاملة التي تعرضت لها بسبب عرقي--
and yes, I don't think I would've been detained if I were white.
أجل، أنا لا أعتقد أنه كان سيتم القبض علي لو كنت أبيضًا.
But actually, what I have in mind today is something else.
ولكن في الواقع، ما يدور في ذهني اليوم هو شيء آخر.
What I have in mind is how much worse things might've been
ما يدور في ذهني هو أنّ الأمور كانت ستكون أسوأ
if I weren't affluent.
لو لم أكن غنيًّا.
I mean, they thought I might be trying to plant an explosive,
لقد ظنّوا أنني كنت أحاول زرع عبوةِ ناسفة،
and they investigated that possibility for an hour and a half,
وقاموا بالتحقيق في هذا الاحتمال لمدة ساعة ونصف،
but I was never put in handcuffs,
ولكن لم يتم تكبيلي بالأصفاد،
I was never taken to a jail cell.
ولم أُنقل أبدًا إلى زنزانة سجن.
I think if I were from one of Washington DC's poor communities of color,
أعتقد أنني إذا كنت من إحدى مجتمعات الفقراء السود في واشنطن العاصمة،
and they thought I was endangering officers' lives,
وظنّوا أنني كنت أهدِّد حياة الضباط،
things might've ended differently.
فإن الأموركانت ستنتهي نهايةً مختلفة.
And in fact, in our system, I think it's better to be an affluent person
في الواقع، أعتقد أنه وفي نظامنا من الأفضل أن تكون شخصًا غنيًّا
suspected of trying to blow up a police station
مُشتَبَهًا بمحاولة تفجير مركز للشرطة
than it is to be a poor person
على أن تكون شخصًا فقيرًا
who's suspected of much, much less than this.
مُشتَبَهًا بأقل من ذلك بكثير.
I want to give you an example from my current work.
أريد أن أقدم لكم مثالًا من عملي الحالي.
Right now, I'm working at a civil rights organization in DC,
أنا أعمل حاليًا في منظمة للحقوق المدنية في واشنطن،
called Equal Justice Under Law.
تُدعى "عدالة متساوية في ظل القانون".
Let me start by asking you all a question.
اسمحوا لي أن أبدأ بطرح سؤال عليكم جميعًا.
How many of you have ever gotten a parking ticket in your life?
كم منكم قد حصل في السابق على مخالفة وقوف؟
Raise your hand.
ارفعوا أيديكم.
Yeah. So have I.
نعم. أنا أيضًا.
And when I had to pay it,
وحينما كان علي دفع الغرامة،
it felt annoying and it felt bad,
كان الأمر مزعجًا وشعرت بإحساس سيئ،
but I paid it and I moved on.
ولكنني دفعتها وطويت الصفحة.
I'm guessing most of you have paid your tickets as well.
أنا أظن أن معظمكم قد دفع الغرامة الخاصة به كذلك.
But what would happen if you couldn't afford the amount on the ticket
ولكن ماذا سيحدث لو لم تستطع تحمل المبلغ
and your family doesn't have the money either, what happens then?
وعائلتك لا تملك المال أيضًا، ماذا سيحدث؟
Well, one thing that's not supposed to happen under the law is,
حسنًا، الشيء الوحيد الذي ليس من المفترض أن يحدث في ظل القانون،
you're not supposed to be arrested and jailed
هو أنه ليس من المفترض أن يتم القبض عليك وسجنك
simply because you can't afford to pay.
لمجرد أنك لا تستطيع أن تدفع.
That's illegal under federal law.
هذا ممنوع بموجب القانون الاتحادي.
But that's what local governments across the country are doing
ولكن هذا هو ما تقوم به الحكومات المحلية في جميع أنحاء البلاد
to people who are poor.
تجاه الأشخاص الفقراء.
And so many of our lawsuits at Equal Justice Under Law
والكثير من الدعاوى القضائية لدينا في "عدالة متساوية في ظل القانون"
target these modern-day debtors' prisons.
تستهدف سجون المدينين الحديثة هذه.
One of our cases is against Ferguson, Missouri.
إحدى قضايانا هي ضد فيرغسون، ولاية ميسوري.
And I know when I say Ferguson,
وأنا أعرف أنني عندما أقول فيرغسون،
many of you will think of police violence.
سيستحضر الكثيرون منكم عنف الشرطة.
But today I want to talk about a different aspect
ولكن اليوم أريد أن أتحدث عن جانب مختلف
of the relationship between their police force and their citizens.
من العلاقة بين شرطة ومواطني فيرغسون.
Ferguson was issuing an average of over two arrest warrants,
كانت فيرغسون تُصدر مايعادل أكثر من مذَكِّرتَي توقيف،
per person, per year,
للشخص في السنة،
mostly for unpaid debt to the courts.
معظمها تخص الديون غير المسددة للمَحاكم.
When I imagine what that would feel like if, every time I left my house,
عندما أتخيل إحساس أنه، في كل مرة أغادر منزلي،
there was a chance a police officer would run my license plate,
هناك فرصة استعلام ضابط شرطة عن رقم لوحة سيارتي،
see a warrant for unpaid debt,
رؤية أن هناك مذكرة ديون غير مسددة،
seize my body they way the did in DC
استجوابي كما فعلوا في العاصمة
and then take me to a jail cell,
ثم أخذي إلى زنزانة السجن،
I feel a little sick.
يعتريني شعور بالمرض.
I've met many of the people in Ferguson who have experienced this,
لقد قابلت الكثير من الناس في فيرجسون الذين عايشوا هذا،
and I've heard some of their stories.
وسمعت بعض قصصهم.
In Ferguson's jail,
في سجن فيرجسون،
in each small cell, there's a bunk bed and a toilet,
في كل زنزانة صغيرة، هناك سرير بطابقين ومرحاض،
but they'd pack four people into each cell.
ولكنهم يضعون أربعة أشخاص في كل زنزانة.
So there'd be two people on the bunks and two people on the floor,
لذلك يكون هناك شخصين على السرير وشخصين على الأرض،
one with nowhere to go except right next to the filthy toilet,
أحدهما لا مكان يذهب إليه إلا بجوار المرحاض القذر،
which was never cleaned.
الذي لم يُنظف أبدًا.
In fact, the whole cell was never cleaned,
في الواقع، الزنزانة بالكامل لم تُنظف أبدًا،
so the floor and the walls were lined with blood and mucus.
لذلك فالأرضية والجدران مغطَّاة بالدم والمخاط.
No water to drink,
لا توجد مياه للشرب،
except coming out of a spigot connected to the toilet.
سوى تلك التي تأتي من حنفيّة متّصلة بالمرحاض.
The water looked and tasted dirty,
كان للمياه مظهر وطعم قذر،
there was never enough food,
لم يكن هناك ما يكفي من الغذاء،
never any showers,
لا حمامات إِطْلاقاً،
women menstruating without any hygiene products,
تحِيض النساء دون أي منتجات نظافة،
no medical attention whatsoever.
ولا عناية طبية من أي نوع.
When I asked a woman about medical attention,
عندما سألت امرأة عن الرعاية الطبية،
she laughed, and she said, "Oh, no, no.
ضحكت، وقالت: "أوه، لا، لا،
The only attention you get from the guards in there is sexual."
الرعاية الوحيدة التي تحصل عليها من الحرّاس هناك هي جنسية."
So, they'd take the debtors to this place and they'd say,
فلقد كانوا يأخذون المدينين إلى هذا المكان، ويقولون:
"We're not letting you leave until you make a payment on your debt."
"نحن لن نسمح لك بالذهاب حتى تدفع الديون الخاصة بك."
And if you could -- if you could call a family member
وإذا كنت تستطيع فعل ذلك -- إذا كنت تستطيع الاتصال بأحد أفراد العائلة
who could somehow come up with some money,
الذي يمكنه أن يأتي بطريقة أو بأخرى ببعض المال،
then maybe you were out.
فلربما قد تخرج.
If it was enough money, you were out.
إذا كان المال كافيًا، فستخرج.
But if it wasn't, you'd stay there for days or weeks,
ولكن إذا لم يكن كذلك، فستبقى هناك لأيام أو أسابيع،
and every day the guards would come down to the cells
وفي كل يوم يأتي الحرّاس إلى الزنزانات
and haggle with the debtors about the price of release that day.
ويساومون مع المدينين عن ثمن الإفراج لذلك اليوم.
You'd stay until, at some point, the jail would be booked to capacity,
ستبقى هناك حتى، في مرحلة ما، يتخطى السجن قدرته الاستيعابية،
and they'd want to book someone new in.
وسيرغبون في إضافة شخص جديد.
And at that point, they'd think,
وفي هذه المرحلة، سيفكرون،
You're out, they're in, and the machine kept moving like that.
فيُخرجونك ويُدخلونه، وهكذا دواليك.
I met a man who,
التقيت رجلاً،
nine years ago, was arrested for panhandling in a Walgreens.
اعتُقِل قبل تسع سنوات بتهمة التسول في ولغرين.
He couldn't afford his fines and his court fees from that case.
لم يكن يستطيع تحمّل الغرامات ورسوم المحكمة الخاصة بهذه القضية.
When he was young he survived a house fire,
عندما كان شابًا نجا من حريق منزل،
only because he jumped out of the third-story window to escape.
فقط لأنه قفز من نافذة الطابق الثالث للفرار.
But that fall left him with damage to his brain
ولكن ذلك خلف لديه أضرارًا على مستوى الدماغ
and several parts of this body, including his leg.
وعدة أجزاء من الجسم، بما في ذلك ساقه.
So he can't work,
لذا فهو لا يستطيع العمل،
and he relies on social security payments to survive.
ويعتمد على مدفوعات الضمان الاجتماعي من أجل العيش.
When I met him in his apartment,
عندما التقيت به في شقته،
he had nothing of value there -- not even food in his fridge.
لم يكن يملك هناك أي شيء ذو قيمة -- ولا حتى موادً غذائية في الثلاجة.
He's chronically hungry.
كان يعاني من الجوع المزمن.
He had nothing of value in his apartment except a small piece of cardboard
لم يكن يملك أي شيء ذو قيمة في شقته باستثناء قطعةٍ صغيرةٍ من الورق المقوى
on which he'd written the names of his children.
كتب عليها أسماء أطفاله.
He cherished this a lot. He was happy to show it to me.
كان يعتز بهذا كثيرًا. كان سعيدًا حينما أراني إياها.
But he can't pay his fines and fees because he has nothing to give.
لكنه لا يستطيع دفع الغرامات والرسوم الخاصة به لأنه ليس لديه ما يمنحه.
In the last nine years, he's been arrested 13 times,
في السنوات التسع الماضية، تم اعتقاله 13 مرة،
and jailed for a total of 130 days on that panhandling case.
وسُجِن لمدة ما مجموعه 130 يومًا في قضية التسول.
One of those stretches lasted 45 days.
استمرت واحدة من تلك الامتدادات 45 يومًا.
Just imagine spending from right now until sometime in June
ولكم أن تتخيلوا قضاء مدة تمتد من الآن حتى وقت ما في شهر يونيو
in the place that I described to you a few moments ago.
في المكان الذي وصفته لكم قبل لحظات قليلة.
He told me about all the suicide attempts he's seen in Ferguson's jail;
أخبرني عن جميع محاولات الانتحار التى رأى في سجن فيرجسون.
about the time a man found a way to hang himself
عن تلك المرة التي وجد فيها رجل طريقة لشنق نفسه
out of reach of the other inmates,
بعيدًا عن متناول السجناء الآخرين،
so all they could do was yell and yell and yell,
لذلك فكل ما كان بإمكانهم فعله هو الصراخ والصراخ والصراخ ،
trying to get the guards' attention
في محاولة للفت انتباه الحراس
so they could come down and cut him down.
حتى يتمكنوا من القدوم وقطع الحبل.
And he told me that it took the guards over five minutes to respond,
وأخبرني أن استجابة الحراس استغرقت خمس دقائق،
and when they came, the man was unconscious.
ولما أتوا، كان الرجل فاقدًا للوعي.
So they called the paramedics and the paramedics went to the cell.
لذلك نادوا على المسعفين وذهب المسعفون إلى الزنزانة.
They said, "He'll be OK,"
وقالوا: "سيكون بخير"،
so they just left him there on the floor.
تركوه هناك على الأرض بكلّ بساطة.
I heard many stories like this and they shouldn't have surprised me,
لقد سمعت قصصًا كثيرة من هذا القبيل وكان ينبغي أن لا تُفاجأني،
because suicide is the single leading cause of death in our local jails.
لأن الانتحار هو السبب الرئيسي للوفاة في السجون المحلية الخاصة بنا.
This is related to the lack of mental health care in our jails.
ويرتبط هذا بعدم وجود الرعاية الصحية النفسية في سجوننا.
I met a woman, single mother of three, making seven dollars an hour.
التقيت امرأة، أم عازبة لثلاثة أطفال، تجني سبعة دولارات في الساعة.
She relies on food stamps to feed herself and her children.
تعتمد على الكوبونات الغذائية لإطعام نفسها وأطفالها.
About a decade ago,
منذ حوالي عشر سنوات،
she got a couple of traffic tickets and a minor theft charge,
حصلت على مخالفتي مرور وتهمة سرقة غير خطيرة،
and she can't afford her fines and fees on those cases.
ولا يمكنها تحمل غرامات ورسوم تلك القضايا.
Since then, she's been jailed about 10 times on those cases,
ومنذ ذلك الحين، سُجنت نحو 10 مرات بسبب تلك القضايا،
but she has schizophrenia and bipolar disorder,
ولكنها تعاني من انفصام الشخصية والاضطراب الثنائي القطب،
and she needs medication every day.
وتحتاج للدواء يوميًّا.
She doesn't have access to those medications in Ferguson's jail,
لا تستطيع الحصول على تلك الأدوية في سجن فيرجسون،
because no one has access to their medications.
لأن لا أحد يستطيع الحصول على الأدوية.
She told me about what it was like to spend two weeks in a cage,
وأوضحت ما يعنيه قضاء أسبوعين في قفص،
hallucinating people and shadows and hearing voices,
تهلوس حول الناس والظلال، وتسمع أصواتًا،
begging for the medication that would make it all stop,
وتتسول لأجل مخدرات من شأنها وقف كل ذلك،
only to be ignored.
ولكن من دون جدوى.
And this isn't anomalous, either:
وهذه ليست حالةً شاذةً حتى:
thirty percent of women in our local jails have serious mental health needs
30٪ من النساء في سجوننا المحلية يعانين من اضطراباتٍ نفسيةٍ حادة
just like hers,
مثلها بالضبط،
but only one in six receives any mental health care while in jail.
ولكن واحدة فقط من أصل ستة فقط هي من تتلقى الرعاية الصحة في السجن.
And so, I heard all these stories about this grotesque dungeon
وكنت قد سمعت قصصًا حول هذه الزنزانة البشعة
that Ferguson was operating for its debtors,
التي تديرها شرطة فيرغسون للنزلاء المدينين،
and when it came time for me to actually see it
وعندما حان وقت رؤيتي لها فعليًّا
and to go visit Ferguson's jail,
وزيارة سجن فيرجسون،
I'm not sure what I was expecting to see,
لم أكن متأكداً مما كان يمكن توقعه،
but I wasn't expecting this.
ولكن لم أكن أتوقع هذا.
It's an ordinary government building.
إنه مبنى حكومي عادي.
It could be a post office or a school.
يمكن أن يكون مكتب بريد أو مدرسة.
It reminded me that these illegal extortion schemes
وذكَّرني بمخططات الابتزاز غير المشروعة هذه
aren't being run somewhere in the shadows,
لا تجري في الخفاء،
they're being run out in the open by our public officials.
بل يديرها مسؤولون لنا علناً.
They're a matter of public policy.
إنها مسألة سياسة عامة.
And this reminded me that poverty jailing in general,
وذكَّرني هذا بأن سجن الفقراء عموماً،
even outside the debtors' prison context,
حتى خارج سياق سجن المدينين،
plays a very visible and central role in our justice system.
يلعب دورًا واضحًا جدًا ومركزيًّا في نظامنا القضائي.
What I have in mind is our policy of bail.
ما يدور في ذهني هو سياسة الكفالة لدينا.
In our system, whether you're detained or free,
في نظامنا، سواء كنت محتجزًا أم لا،
pending trial is not a matter of how dangerous you are
انتظار المحاكمة ليس متعلقًا بمدى خطورتك
or how much of a flight risk you pose.
أو نسبة احتمال فرارك.
It's a matter of whether you can afford to post your bail amount.
بل هي متعلّقة بقدرتك على دفع مبلغ كفالتك.
So Bill Cosby, whose bail was set at a million dollars,
ف(بيل كوسبي)، الذي تم تحديد كفالتة في مليون دولار،
immediately writes the check, and doesn't spend a second in a jail cell.
قام بتحرير شيك على الفور، ولم يُمضي ولا ثانية واحدة في زنزانة السجن.
But Sandra Bland, who died in jail,
ولكن (ساندرا بلاند)، التي توفيت في السجن،
was only there because her family was unable to come up with 500 dollars.
كانت هناك فقط لأن أسرتها لم تتمكن من توفير 500 دولار.
In fact, there are half a million Sandra Blands across the country --
في الواقع، هناك نصف مليون (ساندرا بلاند) في جميع أنحاء البلاد --
500,000 people who are in jail right now,
500000 من السجناء الآن،
only because they can't afford their bail amount.
فقط لأنهم لا يستطيعون تحمّل مبلغ كفالتهم.
We're told that our jails are places for criminals,
قيل لنا أن سجوننا هي أماكن للمجرمين،
but statistically that's not the case:
ولكن الأمر ليس كذلك إحصائيًّا:
three out of every five people in jail right now are there pretrial.
ثلاثة من كل خمسة أشخاص في السجن الآن هناك دون محاكمة.
They haven't been convicted of any crime;
لم تتم إدانتهم بارتكاب أية جريمة؛
they haven't pled guilty to any offense.
لم يتم الإقرار بأنهم مذنبون بأية جريمة.
Right here in San Francisco,
هنا في سان فرانسيسكو،
85 percent of the inmates in our jail in San Francisco
85 في المئة من السجناء في سجننا في سان فرانسيسكو
are pretrial detainees.
عبارة عن محتجزين ينتظرون المحاكمة.
This means San Francisco is spending something like 80 million dollars
وهذا يعني أن سان فرانسيسكو تنفق حوالي 80 مليون دولار
every year
سنويًّا
to fund pretrial detention.
لتمويل احتجازات ما قبل المحاكمة.
Many of these people who are in jail only because they can't post bail
العديد من هؤلاء الذين يتواجدون في السجن فقط لأنهم لا يستطيعون دفع الكفالة
are facing allegations so minor
يواجهون اتهامات طفيفة
that the amount of time it would take for them to sit waiting for trial
بحيث أن مقدار الوقت الذي سيستغرقه انتظارهم للمحاكمة
is longer than the sentence they would receive if convicted,
أطول من مدة الحكم التي سينالونها إذا ما تمت إدانتهم،
which means they're guaranteed to get out faster
مما يعني أنهم سيضمنون خروجًا أسرع
if they just plead guilty.
إذا ما اعترفوا باقتراف الجريمة.
So now the choice is:
والخيار الآن هو:
Should I stay here in this horrible place,
هل يجب عليَّ البقاء هنا في هذا المكان الرهيب،
away from my family and my dependents,
بعيدًا عن عائلتي ومن أعيلهم،
almost guaranteed to lose my job,
مع وجود احتمالٍ كبيرٍ بأن أفقد وظيفتي،
and then fight the charges?
ومن ثم أواجه هذه الاتهامات؟
Or should I just plead guilty to whatever the prosecutor wants and get out?
أم هل ينبغي عليَّ أن أعترف بكل ما يريده المدعي العام ومن ثم أخرج؟
And at this point, they're pretrial detainees, not criminals.
وفي هذه المرحلة، هم محتجزون دون محاكمة، وليسوا مجرمين.
But once they take that plea deal, we'll call them criminals,
ولكن بمجرد أن يختاروا طريق الاعتراف، سوف ندعوهم مجرمين،
even though an affluent person would never have been in this situation,
على الرغم من أن أي شخص ثري لن يكون في هذا الوضع أبدًا،
because an affluent person would have simply been bailed out.
لأن الشخص الثري ببساطة سيدفع الكفالة.
At this point you might be wondering,
عند هذه النقطة، قد تتساءلون،
"This guy's in the inspiration section, what is he doing --
"هذا الرجل في قسم الإلهام، ماذا يفعل -
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
"This is extremely depressing. I want my money back."
"هذا محبط للغاية. أريد استرجاع أموالي"
But in actuality,
ولكن في واقع الأمر،
I find talking about jailing much less depressing than the alternative,
أجد التحدث عن السَّجْنِ أقل كآبة بكثير من البديل،
because I think if we don't talk about these issues
لأنني أعتقد أننا إذا لم نتحدث عن هذه القضايا
and collectively change how we think about jailing,
ونغير بشكل جماعي الطريقة التي نفكر بها حول السَّجْنِ،
at the end of all of our lives,
في نهاية حياتنا جميعًا،
we'll still have jails full of poor people who don't belong there.
ستبقى لدينا سجون مليئة بالناس الفقراء الذين لا ينتمون إلى هناك.
That really is depressing to me.
هذا حقًا هو ما يصيبني بالاكتئاب.
But what's exciting to me is the thought that these stories can move us
ولكن ما يثيرني هو فكرة أن هذه القصص يمكن أن تدفعنا
to think about jailing in different terms.
إلى التفكير في السجن بعبارات مختلفة.
Not in sterile policy terms like "mass incarceration,"
لا بعبارات السياسة العقيمة مثل "السجن الشامل"
or "sentencing of nonviolent offenders,"
أو "الحكم على الجرائم غير العنيفة"،
but in human terms.
ولكن بعبارات إنسانية.
When we put a human being in a cage for days or weeks or months
عندما نضع إنسانًا في قفص لمدة أيام أو أسابيع أو أشهر
or even years,
أو حتى سنوات،
what are we doing to that person's mind and body?
ما هو تأثير ذلك على ذهن وجسد ذلك الشخص؟
Under what conditions are we really willing to do that?
تحت أي ظروف نحن حقًا على استعداد للقيام بذلك؟
And so if starting with a few hundred of us in this room,
إذا كان كل واحد منا في هذه القاعة،
we can commit to thinking about jailing in this different light,
سيلتزم بالتفكير في السَّجْنِ في ضوء مختلف،
then we can undo that normalization I was referring to earlier.
فيمكننا تغيير ذلك التطبيع الذي أشرت إليه سابقًا.
If I leave you with anything today, I hope it's with the thought
إذا كنت سأترك لديكم أي أثر اليوم، فآمل أن يكون هو الاعتقاد
that if we want anything to fundamentally change --
بأننا إذا كنا نريد شيئًا ما أن يتغير جذريًّا --
not just to reform our policies on bail and fines and fees --
ليس فقط إصلاح سياساتنا المرتبطة بالكفالة والغرامات والرسوم --
but also to make sure that whatever new policies replace those
ولكن أيضا التأكد من أن أي سياسات جديدة تحلّ محل السابقة
don't punish the poor and the marginalized in their own new way.
لن تعاقب الفقراء والمهمشين بطريقة أخرى جديدة.
If we want that kind of change,
إذا كنا نريد هذا النوع من التغيير،
then this shift in thinking is required of each of us.
فإن هذا التحوّل في التفكير مطلوب من كل واحد منّا.
Thank you.
شكرًا.
(Applause)
(تصفيق)